「ハンター」と呼ぶ 人は　彼らを… その力に魅せられた すごい奴らがいる 「未知」という言葉が放つ魔力 財宝 珍獣 怪獣 秘境 魔境 秘宝
Tonight, at 9 PM, the mummy of Princess Corco
will be auctioned off.
「今　第３次試験まで クリアしました　すごいでしょ？
Everyone's here...
でも　ここまで来るのは 大変だったんだよ」。
These are mostly Mafia leaders. We even have some head honchos here.
「けど　そこで俺は
Their honor's on the line.
レオリオとクラピカに 出会ったんだ！」。 品性は 金で買えないんだよ　レオリオ。
For each winning bid, five percent goes back into the
Mafia community as a commission. Does that act as a bribe?
３度目だぜ。 表へ出な。
Like, the more they bid,
the more they'll receive?
その薄汚いクルタ族の血ってやつを 絶やしてやるぜ。 取り消せ　レオリオ！
Yeah, that's how the Mafia flexes
its financial muscles.
取り消せ…。
So this is a chance to improve
their standings.
「レオリオさん」だ。
But some gangs have gone bust
クソっ！ クソっ！
Welcome, everyone.
ありがとう　ゴン！　命の恩人だ！
Die.
いや　礼には及ばぬ。
My Ambidextrous Automatic Weapons
Double Machine Gun
まぁ　あれだ… 助かってよかったな。
Get down! Black Balloons!
はい！　それじゃあ　俺 持ち場に戻ります！
Guard me.
あ…。 フッ…。
Thankless Heroes
Eleven Black Children
すまなかった　レオリオさん。
Is he using Nen bullets?!
な…　何だよ　いきなり。 水くせぇ。
That means he's also an Emitter!
レオリオでいいよ　レオリオで。
He'll break through my Nen barrier, and pierce my body...
俺も悪かったな。 さっきの言葉は　全面撤回する。
Each bullet packs an incredible punch!
すまなかった。
Run!
「このことが きっかけで　俺達３人は
Inform the boss—
「でも　その道のりは 簡単じゃなかった」。
Baise, you go ahead...
俺は　こいつに説教してやんねえと 気が治まらねえ！
That was way too fast...
落ち着け　レオリオ！ これが落ち着いていられるか！
I didn't get to do anything.
せっかくの合格を棒に振る気か!?
All yours, Shizuku.
へ？　合格？
Let's go, Blinky.
我々は正解したんだよ 「沈黙」　それが正しい答えなんだ。 妻を… 妻を助けてくれ…。
Suck up the bodies, blood, body parts, and all their possessions.
レオリオ！　ケガ人を頼む！
Grab the chairs, too.
君　誰？ ゲッ。
Shizuku's Nen ability is always
entertaining to watch. Oh?
何で　俺が さっきの奴とは別だと分かった？ えっ？　だって 顔が　全然　違うじゃん。
Someone's still alive.
声だって　君のほうが 少し高くて　細い感じだし。
Wh-Who are you?
クックック…　フハハ…！
Doesn't matter. You're all dead...
アハハハ…！
The community will
何？ 俺　何か　おかしいこと言った？
destroy you.
お前の　その　とてつもなく 人間離れした運動能力　観察力
Your family! Torture you... Cut you up.
ハンター試験を受けるに 十分　値する。
You'll taste hell!
うん。 イッヒヒ！
Family? What's that?
大変お待たせいたしました。 ただ今をもって
I'm having difficulty hearing clearly, but there's a real commotion
inside the building.
ハンター受験者の受付時間を 終了いたします。
Something must have happened. Contact the leader!
では　これより ハンター試験を開始いたします！
Got it. I'll contact Linssen and Basho.
お？
You two head inside!
「２次試験会場まで 私に　ついて来ること」。
What? There's no one here.
これが１次試験でございます。
Where did they go?
Search the place!
「その中で俺は キルアっていう同い年の男の子と 仲良くなったんだ」。
Hey, what happened to
the merchandise? Underground... Head underground, now!
ねぇ　君　いくつ？ １２歳。
It appears that everyone in the
auction house has disappeared.
ふん　同い年ね
What? The whole place is in an uproar.
やっぱ俺も　走ろうっと！
What about the merchandise?
おぉ　カッコいい！
Melody is heading underground, to the safe.
俺　キルア。 俺は　ゴン！
I-It's empty...
ねぇ　キルアは　何で ハンターになりたいの？
The goods for today's auction
have been stolen!
俺？　別にハンターになんか なりたくないよ。
Who did this?! Damn!
えっ？
Where'd they go?
ものすごい難関だって 言われてるから
Split up and search, fool!
面白そうだと思っただけさ。
Send word to every gang...
けど　拍子抜けだな。
Quickly!
ゴンは？
Okay, understood.
俺はさ　親父がハンターなんだ。 で　俺も親父みたいなハンターに なりたいと思って。
We'll catch those thieves.
ふん 親父って　どんなハンター？ 分かんない。
I'll head over. Rendezvous with Linssen and Basho
behind the building, in Central Park.
プッ　アハハハ！ お前　それじゃ　変じゃん！
Squala...
そう？ だって　親父みたいになりたいのに 親父のこと分かんないなんてさ。
Yes? Just in case, leave five dogs behind. Right. Listen up!
俺　生まれて　すぐ ミトさんに育てられたから
Don't take your eyes off the boss!
親父は写真でしか知らないんだ。
Don't let anyone in the
room until we return.
誰だよ　ミトさんって。
Yes.
ミトおばさん。 はぁ。
All roads are sealed.
親父も１２歳の時に ハンター試験　受けたんだってさ！
The only remaining escape
route is by air! If you see any suspicious
aircraft, contact me.
合格して　ハンターになって そして　島を出て行った。
Make sure not to kill them.
俺を捨ててまで 夢中になったハンターって
The community has offered
a substantial reward to the gang that captures the thieves.
どんなんだろうって。
You must take them alive!
ゴール！ ゴール！
No, the safe was empty.
やった！　俺の勝ち！ 何　言ってんだ！ 俺のほうが早かっただろ！
According to the auctioneer,
the only one who knew the situation, everything in the safe had been
moved a few hours earlier.
さて ゲームのルールじゃが
Exactly as though they
expected this to happen.
この船が 次の目的地に着くまでに
Don't you find the timing too perfect?
この球を　わしから奪えば おぬしらの勝ちじゃ。
We have a...
よっ　ほっ　はっ　ほっ　ほ！
Judas among us.
ハッ。
We have a Judas among us.
もらった！ もらった！
You're saying that one of us is a traitor?
うわ！ うわ！
There are no traitors.
うぎゅ！　あっ。 うっ。 はぁ。
Besides, Judas wasn't a traitor.
努力賞といったとこじゃの。
It's said that Judas sold Jesus out
for thirty pieces of silver.
「キルアといると…」。
But how much would a traitor ask
「ハンター試験も楽しいよ！
from the Mafia?
今では　大の仲良しさ」　フフ…。
Consider the merits...
すごい人達で　いっぱいなんだ」。
that any of us cares for those things? It's unlikely...
やるねぇ　坊や。
Assuming there were a spy, the response was too tepid. If they had foreknowledge
それ釣り竿？　面白い武器だね。
that Class-A bounties would
appear at the auction, they would have increased security.
見せてよ　それ。 てめぇの相手は俺だ！
The auction goers were all
uninformed and unarmed. That's true.
ダァ！
I believe that someone
あっ　うぅ…。
provided information
that wasn't explicit.
仲間を助けに来たのかい？
However, a Mafia community leader
いい子だね。
believed that information.
ん　いい顔だ。
I don't get it...
うっ　うっ　うっ…。 うっ　うぅ！
Who told who what?
いいね。
Whatever. So what do we do?
ゾクゾクして来たよ。
Did you ask the auctioneer
ハァ！
he swore on his life that he didn't know.
うっ。 ぐっ　うぅ…。
Feitan tortured him, so he wasn't lying.
うぅ…。
He had the worst luck of them all today.
実に　いい。
Did you get the names of
anyone who might know?
いい顔だぁ！
You bet I did.
ぐっ　うぅ…。 ゴホっ　ゴホっ…。 安心して。
The auction is run by the
Mafia community heads, who lead gangs in each of the
ten districts around the world.
君の仲間は　殺しちゃいないよ。 彼は合格だから。
They're called the Ten Dons. This is the only time that all
ten gather in one place, to discuss business and issue orders.
フフフ…。 うん！　君も合格。
Their commands are carried
out by a special force, the Shadow Beasts.
いいハンターになりなよ。
This squad consists of each
don's best combatants.
ハァハァ…。
I see, then...
でも　俺 あの時　ワクワクしたんだ。 怖くて逃げ出したいって 思ったけど　それもできなくて…。
Since the Shadow Beasts weren't
guarding the auction house, the Mafia didn't know we were coming. That makes sense.
でも　ワクワクしたんだ　変だよね。
Then how did they move
the merchandise?
第３次試験会場に到着した時には ４１人まで減っていたんだ」。
The twenty-five square-meter
safe was packed with
あぁ　オホン。 皆様　３次試験の スタート地点は　ここ
items ready to be auctioned off.
「トリックタワー」と呼ばれる塔の てっぺんとなります。
The Shadow Beast walked in, then
walked right back out, empty-handed.
トリックタワー？ 合格の条件は　この塔を 生きて下まで下りて来ること。
But the safe was emptied.
制限時間は　７２時間です。
He must possess a Nen power
similar to Shizuku's.
なっ　何だよ　ここ…。
Probably. Surely they noticed
見ろよ　あそこ。
after five hundred people disappeared...
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　諸君　説明しよう。
Can we let loose?
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　諸君らの前にいるのは
Naturally.
このトリックタワーに 幽閉されている囚人達だ。
Put on a show for the pursuers.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　彼らは同時に　審査委員会から 正式に任命を受けた
That will draw them out.
雇われ試験官でもある。 [ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　諸君には　これから　ここで 彼ら５人と戦ってもらう。
I can't wait...
相手の出方が測れない分 初戦は　リスクが大きい。
Up there! It's them! They're in a hot air balloon!
ここは　私が…。
The balloon is moving toward
the Gordeau Desert!
いや　俺が行こう！
We're in pursuit! Hot air balloon?
トンパさん!?
Not an airship?
ふん！　ん…！
It's possible that we aren't dealing
勝負！
with an ordinary band of armed thugs.
フンっ　ア！
Contact the Ten Dons.
ま　参ったぁ！ はぁ？ 何？
Ask them to immediately
dispatch the Shadow Beasts!
もしかして 「参った」って言ったの？
Roger that.
おい　見ろよ　ゴンのローソク 急に勢いが増して来たぜ。
Come down here!
恐らく　軸の中に火薬か何かを 混ぜて　火力を増大させ
We'll even let you decide whether
you'll be drowned or buried!
ロウの消耗を速めているのだろう。
There's a whole crowd...
イヒ！ 火の勢いが強いってことは
I don't have to suck them up, do I? No, they don't matter.
ちょっとの風じゃ 消えないってことだよね。
Hey! Stay out of this.
速い！
I'll handle it...
１２本の脚を持つクモの入れ墨 あれは…。
Are you the ones who
kidnapped the guests? Yeah.
俺様は　「旅団」四天王の１人 マジタニ！
Well, you do have guts. Who's your leader?
よし！ こうなったら　ジャンケンだ！
An ordinary gun wouldn't
even scratch him.
ジャンケンで　どっちが勝つか 懸けようぜ！
Physically, he's the strongest.
ウッフフ…。 何だよ？
It's like watching a gorilla stomping ants.
あなたの出す　てが 手に取るように分かるわ。
Oh?
えっ。 私は　人の心が読めるのよ。
More of them. They came all the way here,
merely to be killed.
ウソつけ！　ハッタリかまして 俺を動揺させようたって
Just watching isn't any fun. Let's play cards.
そうは　いかねえぞ！ やってみれば分かるわ。
Yes. I agree.
行くわよ。 あぁ！
Boss!
さぁ！　次は何を出すの？ 考えて！　ほら　ウフフフ…。
That wasn't enough to warm me
up for the Shadow Beasts.
あいこで…。 しょ！
Ow...
アッハハハ…！　私の勝ち。
A rifle? How annoying. Trying to take me out from afar?
これから行われるのは 一方的な惨殺さ。
Yeah! Bull's-eye!
試験も恩赦も　俺には興味がない。
That's enough!
お前は　ただ 泣き叫んでいればいい。
Don't get too cocky, monster.
そう　ＯＫ。 じゃあ 死んだほうが負けでいいね。
This super-bazooka is strong
enough to take out a tank.
ああ　そういうことだ。
You'll be blown to smithereens!
お前の亡きがらは
How sad...
俺様が　この手でバラバラに…。
You're comparing me
to some little tank?
それ…　お　俺の…？
That kinda hurt...
か…　返して…。
None of you will escape!
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ] それでは道を選んでください。
The advance force was obliterated.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　選択は２つ。
Guns are ineffective against him.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　「５人で行けるが 長く困難な道」。
Impossible...
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　もう１つは 「３人しか行けないが 短く簡単な道」。
See for yourself. His aura is unbelievable. As is the number of corpses.
俺は「○」を押すよ。 やっぱり　みんなで せっかく　ここまで来たんだから
Who is that guy?
５人で通過したい。
He's tearing through people
like scraps of paper.
ゴン…。 イチかバチかの可能性でも
We're supposed to capture him?
俺は　そっちに懸けたいんだ。
I won't be part of that! I agree.
えいっ。 ふん！ ふん！ えいっ。
I don't see how we can win...
ふん！ えいっ。
However, we cannot abandon
our mission and back off.
壁に穴を開け 短くて簡単な道へ入るなんて…。
I suddenly hear an additional
heartbeat coming from somewhere...
３人か…
I am Worm, a Shadow Beast.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　残り３０秒。 それにしても　ギリギリだったね。
Which group do you belong to?
もう　手がマメだらけだ。 俺もだ！
We're bodyguards for
the Nostrade Family.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ] 第２３号　４０３番　レオリオ。
I see.
手は　マメだらけだけど ５人揃ってタワーを攻略できた。
It seems that you can use Nen, but don't bother.
ホント　ゴンのおかげだな。
These aren't ordinary thugs.
エヘヘ…。
To them, taking lives is like breathing.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　第３次試験終了。
Y-You could say they're
professional killers.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]　通過人数　２５名 うち１名　死亡。
And a pro knows his trade best of all.
「そんなわけで　俺
I-I'm Porcupine.
第３次試験まで 合格したよ　ミトさん！ 残り　ハンター試験が いくつあるか分からないけど
We Shadow Beasts will see to them.
俺　絶対クリアして　親父と同じ ハンターになるからね。
These are the Shadow Beasts...
それじゃ　また！ ゴン＝フリークス」。
The Mafia community has
unleashed the Shadow Beasts on the bandits who attacked the auction.
ジン…　あんたの息子は 着々と　あんたの背中を 追いかけてるわよ。
facing off against the Phantom Troupe.